all right this is stuff that rich people
and poor people have in common but not
the middle class so it's only super poor
and super rich and there's more in
common than you think but the middle
class need not apply here all right so I
thought of this bit when I was working
writing for late night and I thought
about the concept of an outdoor shower
and I thought if you're taking an
outdoor shower you're either super rich
or busted
poor you either buy the Cabana on the
table you know you buy the tennis court
and the pool and everything or in front
with a hose sitting in a tub and a dirt
lawn all right so Rich Man Poor
Man all right greatly affected by the
raising of the minimum
wage you either own 28 t Taco
Bells or you work at one Taco
Bell either way it is
impactful drives a brand of car that no
longer
exists you're
either you're either Jay Leno and a
dusenberg or my stepdad John in a 74 AMC
Matador when you
enter a fancy department store somebody
who works at that department store
rushes toward you yelling may I help
you rich man poor
man never eaten at an Outback
Steakhouse that's me ladies and
gentlemen I was far too poor during my
construction days I could not afford to
go to an Outback Steakhouse and now I'm
far too
wealthy that's for the little people I
call them the Saturn drivers
outraged at the welfare
system you had your bachelor party in
Mexico at a funeral your cofin is pulled
by a
horse all right stick with me
you use a ladder on
Wheels either it's in your policial
library in your estate and it's made of
mahogany or you got a job at the Home
Depot and the guy wants the air
conditioning unit from up
top uh
oh I'm going to try it
you used to live on a
plantation all right let's turn the
page you know the going rate for copper
starred in Bill and Ted's Excellent
Adventure and last but not
least you live next door to a rapper
[Applause]
it's either Beyonce and Jay-Z in
Malibu or you're in Van eyes California
an apartment building and there's a
white kid in the unit above
you who goes by the handle of mayonnaise